Vanished: Searching for My Sister is a tv movie, mystery,
thriller film directed by Timothy Woodward Jr..
Jada gets pulled into a world of drugs and deceit in order to learn the shocking
truth about what really happened to her missing sister, Kayla.
Jada Stallworth/Kayla Davis, played by Tatyana Ali.
Warren Davis, played by Justin Bruening.
Detective Hill, played by Jasmine Guy.
Detective Nichols, played by Carolyn Hennesy.
Eleanor Hewitt, played by Grace Junot.
Gary, played by Bobby Campo.
Robert Joseph Camposecco (born March 9, 1983) known
professionally as Bobby Campo, is an American actor.
Campo made his on-screen debut in the CBS television film Vampire Bats in 2005.
He appeared in a supporting role in the teen comedy film Legally Blondes in 2009, and later received wide
recognition for playing Nick O'Bannon in the supernatural horror film The Final Destination that same year.
Following his breakout, Campo starred in the comedy film General Education (2012) and had a main role as Ben on the YouTube web
series Audrey (2012), as well as a recurring role as Max on the Syfy supernatural television series Being Human (2013).
In the mid-to-late 2010s, Campo had a recurring role as Seth Branson on season 1 of the MTV anthology slasher
series Scream (2015–2016) and starred in the Christian drama film Unbroken: Path to Redemption (2018).
The tone is intense and emotional and mind_bending.